Huh? What the hell?
Why did a powered suit from
Yggdrasil suddenly appear?
Could it be a player?
The Death Knight and Death Warrior
were destroyed so easily...
Mm. Just as expected.
I see. So that's why...
Huh? Cocytus?!
Yes! Yes! Yes! I understand now, too!
Lord Ains was expecting the
one in red armor to appear!
He chose to send fewer soldiers in order
to lure the enemy out into the open!
Excellent deduction from the
two of you, as expected!
Y-Yeah.
Hey, who is that guy?
He's from Drop of Red, one of the
three adamantite teams in the Kingdom.
It's reported that his team normally works
in the northern region of the Kingdom.
S-So that's why Lord Ains set
a trap in this northern city!
So, he's a fish that took the bait...
Exactly.
Now that you've achieved your original goal,
we should send stronger forces to
that town and raze it to the ground.
Yes, that sounds good...
N-No, I was thinking of
changing the plans a bit
and bringing the royal capital
to ruin immediately.
If that is what you wish, we will simply obey.
Yes.
This way, I'll be able to give the people
in that town a chance to escape.
Good! We will cease hiding our movements
and advance on the royal capital!
We will annihilate every city
within our reach along the way.
Teach them the foolishness
of resisting Nazarick!
Yes!
Your Highness,
Princess Renner is here to see you.
I'll speak with her during dinner.
She said that if she can't
speak with you immediately,
she'll begin yelling lies mixed with truth...
I understand. Let her in.
But have the other two
with her stand outside.
I understand.
What is it?
Is Father still alive?
Hey, now. Do you think I'd kill him?
At a time like this?
Father is not well right now.
I'm having him rest.
Brother is able to detain Father even
without Marquis Raeven's soldiers...
That means that the head of the military
and the head of internal
affairs have taken your side.
Father planned to negotiate until the end,
in order to minimize our losses.
I understand his feelings, but...
There had been no word of
the Sorcerer Kingdom invading
since the declaration of war.
But, in reality, his army has been
heading north this whole time.
He took over the northern border
near the Council State
in order to prevent them
from sending support troops.
That's right.
The invaded cities were completely destroyed
and all the people were massacred.
My sister...
Please enlighten me with your brilliant mind.
How have the Sorcerer Kingdom's
forces gone unnoticed until now?
You've realized it yourself, haven't you?
It's the work of the people
in our own kingdom.
But the only person who can keep
this a secret so thoroughly...
...is Marquis Raeven.
No way! Impossible.
This is Marquis Raeven's domain.
That man loves his son quite dearly.
Wouldn't he do it if his
son were taken hostage?
You think they're threatening him that way?
I believe that he's decided that
the royal family has no future.
What action would you take
in a situation like this?
If things continue according
to the movements on this map,
there will be a decisive battle
at the royal capital next.
Yes.
Do you think we can win?
It's not a matter of winning or losing.
We have to do it.
The Sorcerer Kingdom is burning down all the
cities and murdering all who live in them.
We can only survive by
gathering all the soldiers
and risking everything on
the slim chance of victory.
I'll ask the people, as well.
We'll advertise the cruelty of the
Sorcerer Kingdom and call them to arms.
Brother, you've truly become a king.
Your way of thinking is correct.
I'm completely useless in battle,
but a member of the royal family should
stand on the front lines to lead the troops.
Father should take care of the rest.
You can escape at any time.
I understand.
I'll do so when the time comes.
What're you gonna do?
I'm joining!
Just you wait, Sorcerer King!
Hey, everyone...
Only one person needs to go to
see the contents of the request.
Why don't you guys go and get a drink?
Lakyus, is there a reason
we can't go with you?
O-O-Of course not!
The Drop of Red are coming for
this request, aren't they?
Isn't their leader, Mr. Azuth, your relative?
You guys probably have a lot to
catch up on, right? I get you.
So, you understand?! Then...
That's the mystery.
So strange.
Huh?
What kind of request requires both
the Drop of Red and Blue Rose?
It's suspicious.
Maybe it's a trap.
Yes. We shouldn't act separately.
And we want to meet such a famous hero.
He's a relative, so it wouldn't
hurt to meet him at least once.
This is the meeting place.
Too suspicious.
Someone is definitely planning something.
Come on in.
Um, everyone...
Let me be honest.
My uncle's the type of person
that makes most people grimace.
Hey, Lakyu! Long time no see!
Uncle... Can't you dress a little
more appropriately for this meeting?
Well, now. At least we're not
having a meeting in bed.
Does it really matter?
It matters!
Is that so?
Aw, stop!
And I heard he was a hero...
Leave, women.
Who's this kid?
A brat who doesn't even show her face
shouldn't act so high and mighty!
Charm Person.
You're in the way. Leave.
Oh, yes.
Charm Person.
Go.
I understand.
Evileye.
Good job!
Boss.
You're on time.
Hey, hey, hey...
You're the last ones here and you're
giving off such dangerous vibes.
You're pretty cocky for
bringing whores, old man.
Hah. You're the ones who held
a meeting in a place like this.
I just wanted to harass you guys a bit.
Now, now.
I would appreciate it if
everyone settled down.
Well, Qua's the leader this time,
so I guess I'll listen...
Let me get straight to the point.
Lord Azuth Aindra and the other
absent members from the Drop of Red...
As well as all the members from Blue Rose...
We are here to scout you today.
Which country are you guys from?
Who cares?
What?
No way!
Please be at ease.
If we really planned to kill all of you,
we wouldn't be wasting
time introducing ourselves.
Are you people from the Theocracy?
The Theocracy?!
The Theocracy's elite heroic unit.
The Black Scripture, was it?
I heard one of you deviated
from the heroic path, though.
It seems like you know a lot.
But there are people here who are as
strong as me, maybe even stronger.
Evileye of the Blue Rose.
You'd be a bit troublesome.
Hmph.
Hey.
Theocracy's secret unit.
Want to work with us to fight
against the Sorcerer King?
I see.
I understand your thoughts, Lord Azuth.
And what's the answer from the Blue Rose?
We won't force you by any means.
We want you to truly become our allies
and help secure the future of mankind.
I refuse. How about...
Don't just speak for yourself.
We all agree with Leader's decision.
Yeah.
I see.
Looks like it'd be pointless
to try to convince you.
We hope everyone is able to bring
retribution upon the Sorcerer King.
So...
What are you going to do, Uncle?
I'll wait here for the arrival
of the Sorcerer King.
He'll definitely make his way here.
You guys won't even be able to
get your swords close to him.
Run.
Even so, we can't leave the
royal capital behind.
If you're asking me to join you, I refuse.
I'll be moving on my own.
Do you think you'll be able to do anything?
There's no way I can defeat him.
But if I'm alone,
I should be able to escape, even if the
Sorcerer King surrounds the entire capital.
Welp, I'm going to unload
a bit in the other room.
Sorry for the wait, kittens.
Jeez! You took forever!
Your Highness.
I know.
Lord Ains, a representative is
approaching from the human army.
I am the crown prince of the Re-Estize Kingdom,
Zanac Valleon Igana Ryle Vaiself!
I would like to speak with the Sorcerer King!
What do you wish to do, Lord Ains?
I feel there's no need to listen, unless it's
a messenger announcing the start of battle...
If he refuses to converse with an opponent,
others may think him close-minded.
Who cares about a rumor when
no one is left to spread it?
Albedo. Have you forgotten?
There may be someone watching from
afar who can speak ill of us.
My apologies.
Yes. Then, I will go.
Lord Ains, bring guards with you.
A royal came to me alone.
It is only right that I return the favor.
I am glad to meet you, Sorcerer King.
I am Zanac Valleon Igana Ryle Vaiself.
I am glad to meet you, as well.
I am the Sorcerer King, Ains Ooal Gown.
Will water suffice?
Yes. Thank you very much, Your Majesty.
I appreciate your hospitality.
Now, the preparations for
our talk are complete.
What did you wish to speak about?
Shall I discuss why
our invasion is just?
Your Majesty,
there's something I'd like to ask.
Why are you doing something this cruel?
Why won't you accept our plea of surrender?
Because there is no merit to it.
Merit?
We will sacrifice your kingdom
to show the world that
it is foolish to oppose
the Sorcerer Kingdom.
To that end, we will enter your royal
capital after decimating your forces
and turn everything into
a mountain of rubble.
We'll leave everything like that for
hundreds or even thousands of years...
In this way, stories about the folly
of going against the Sorcerer Kingdom
will be passed down for all eternity.
Why have you chosen to do so?
What?
There are other ways
to have Your Majesty's prestige
known throughout the world.
Why are your actions so close-minded?
Close-minded, huh?
What is your goal?
My goal?
My comrades from Yggdrasil may
exist somewhere in this world.
That's what I had hoped...
My goal...
It seems simple and complicated
at the same time.
My goal...
There's only one thing I'm searching for...
Happiness.
Happiness?
In the end, isn't the ultimate
goal of all creatures happiness?
So, you're saying it's fine to take away the
happiness of others for the sake of your own?
Isn't that obvious?
If I can bring happiness
to the ones I treasure,
I don't care about what
happens to anyone else.
If your people could only achieve happiness
by making the people of another
country suffer, what would you do?
Would you tell your people
to give up on that happiness?
That logic is too extreme!
Excuse me, Your Majesty.
No, I don't mind.
Are you telling me that
someone of Your Majesty's intelligence and
power had no other way to move forward?
There may be other ways.
However, it's better to grab a hold of
the chance to obtain such happiness
if the opportunity to do
so is easily available.
They say, "The goddess of
fortune is bald behind."
What a strange goddess.
Oh, pardon me.
I'm not belittling the gods
you believe in or anything.
Please forgive me.
I don't mind.
I don't particularly believe in them.
So, that's how it is.
I will have you suffer for the happiness
of the people I must protect.
Does my answer satisfy you?
Well, they say it is the
duty of those at the top
to pursue benefits for their country
and bring happiness to their people.
I understand your reason for
refusing our surrender.
It seems there is nothing else I can do.
Now, I guess it's my turn to question you.
That's right.
Who currently holds the sword
that Gazef Stronoff wielded?
The armor you're wearing was
also previously worn by him.
Yes.
A man named Brain Unglaus is currently
in possession of that sword.
Brain Unglaus...
Oh, is that man currently here?
No, he should be in the royal palace.
I see.
Then, it seems it doesn't matter what
spells I use to decimate your forces.
We don't plan to lose,
but I hope you use magic that will
kill us without much suffering.
Well...
We've now become acquainted with one another.
I'll make sure to kill
you as gently as I can.
I appreciate that.
The drink was delicious, Your Majesty.
May I ask you one last thing?
Did you or perhaps one of your
subordinates kill my elder brother?
Your brother?
The deed was probably done by one of mine.
I see. So he's dead, after all.
Thank you for letting me know, Your Majesty.
I'll take my leave.
A dauntless man.
That must be what true royalty is like.
My goal...
There's only one thing I'm searching for...
Happiness.
Perhaps I was never fit to be a king.
I just wanted to make this
kingdom into a respectable one.
Your Highness!
You're safe!
What did the Sorcerer King say?!
The Sorcerer King plans to
massacre everyone in the kingdom.
There was no opportunity for negotiation.
Welcome back.
It sounds like the talk didn't go well.
In other words, the talk went as expected.
I see.
So, what kind of evil monster
was the Sorcerer King?
He was surprisingly human.
What?
Well, he was definitely
a monster on the outside.
But, well, he was the same as
any other human on the inside.
So what is the plan of attack?
There's no plan.
We lost many of our commanders
and knights in the last battle.
Truthfully speaking,
I didn't like Stronoff, so I never thought
I would miss him at a time like this...
You people are...
King Zanac!
Stand down! This is His Highness's tent!
A rebellion at this point and time?
No, this is just the result of
their desperate attempt to live...
You lowly people! Stand down!
Stop, Representative.
For what reason did you enter my tent?
Your Highness, please surrender.
It's impossible.
We can only survive if we
defeat the Sorcerer King.
We can't win!
He has an army of undead!
That may be the case for you, Your Highness.
But we'll exchange your life for our own!
We will go and pledge our
allegiance to the Sorcerer King!
Your Highness, please obey us quietly.
As a member of the royal family,
I have the resolve to fight to the end.
Come, if you don't fear losing your life!
What's wrong?!
Come and take this neck if you can!
Lord Ains.
What is it, Albedo?
Some nobles from the Kingdom
wish to see the Sorcerer King.
Bring them here.
We are in awe of Your Majesty and
wish to bow down at your feet.
Please accept this, Your Majesty.
Bury him with respect.
So, what happened to the
armor this man was wearing?
What's wrong?
You can't answer Lord Ains' question?
N-No! Well, about that...
I believe it's with the
prince's corpse in his tent.
I see. I understand.
You all did well.
I shall give you a reward
comparable to your efforts.
What do you want?
Please spare me and my family!
Sorcerer King!
I pledge my complete allegiance to you!
I do, as well, Your Majesty!
Please show mercy on us!
Me, as well!
I understand. I understand.
Then, I will spare you and your families.
Thank you very much!
Albedo, send them to Neuronist.
Understood.
Thank you!
Long live His Majesty, the Sorcerer King!
Aura.
Yes, Lord Ains.
Make sure to tell Neuronist not to
kill them unless they beg for death.
I understand, Lord Ains!
Even if they beg for death,
don't kill them too quickly.
Yes!
I've lost interest.
Cocytus will be the commander
and Mare the vice-commander.
Yes.
Yes!
I allow the two of you to
freely use your strength...
So don't let a single one of them survive.